<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Right Life</string>
    <string name="title_activity_homepage">HomepageActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="specially_offer_20_off_2499">Specially offer: 20% off <strike>₹ 2499</strike></string>
    <string name="title_activity_rlpage">RLPageActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="article">The fourth-most common mineral in your body is magnesium. Without it, your body cannot function correctly.
        \n\nThe nutrient is necessary for hundreds of metabolic processes as well as numerous other critical biological processes, such as the synthesis of vital proteins and the production of energy. \n\nAmong the dietary sources of magnesium are: \n\n• legumes, seeds, and nuts \n• whole grains \n• green leafy vegetables \n• fish and meat have lower quantities.\n
        Magnesium deficiency is thought to affect 15% to 20% of teenagers and 9% to 17% of adults \n\n A lack of magnesium may contribute to the emergence of diseases like cardiovascular disease, type 2 diabetes, Alzheimer’s disease, and atherosclerosis—an artery constriction brought on by a plaque buildup of cholesterol.</string>

    <string name="str_your_height">Your Height</string>
    <string name="str_enter_your_dob">Enter your date of birth?</string>
    <string name="str_your_weight">Your Weight</string>
    <string name="str_waist">Waist</string>
    <string name="str_blood_pressure">Blood Pressure</string>
    <string name="str_systolic_bp">Systolic Blood Pressure</string>
    <string name="str_diastolic_bp">Diastolic Blood Pressure</string>

    <string name="str_ft_inch">ft.inch</string>
    <string name="str_cms">cms</string>
    <string name="str_kgs">Kgs</string>
    <string name="str_lbs">lbs</string>
    <string name="str_inches">inches</string>

    <string name="dob_error"> User must be at least 15 years old</string>
    <string name="height_error"> User must enter height</string>
    <string name="weight_error"> User must enter weight</string>
    <string name="waist_error"> User must enter waist</string>
    <string name="systolic_range_error"> The Systolic range should be between 40 to 250</string>
    <string name="diastolic_range_error"> The Diastolic range should be between 30 to 300</string>
    <string name="general_error"> Please fill the values</string>

    <string name="MEASUREMENT_CANCELED">"Measurement cancelled"</string>
    <string name="MEASURING_COUNTDOWN">"Measurement starting in..."</string>
    <string name="MEASURING_PERFECT">"Perfect! Please hold still"</string>
    <string name="MEASURING_MSG_DEFAULT">"Please centre your face within the outline"</string>

    <string name="ERR_CAMERA_CALIBRATION_TIMEOUT">"Could not calibrate camera
Restarting calibration..."</string>
    <string name="ERR_CONFLICT_EMAIL">"A user with that email address already exists
Try logging in instead"</string>
    <string name="ERR_CONFLICT_PHONE">"A user with that phone number already exists
Try logging in instead"</string>
    <string name="ERR_CONSTRAINT_BRIGHTNESS">"Your face was too bright
Please try to dim the lights"</string>
    <string name="ERR_CONSTRAINT_DARKNESS">"Your face was not well lit
Please try better lighting"</string>
    <string name="ERR_CONSTRAINT_DISTANCE">"Please move closer to the camera and try again"</string>
    <string name="ERR_CONSTRAINT_FPS">"The camera is not maintaining the required frame rate
Please try closing all background applications"</string>
    <string name="ERR_CONSTRAINT_GAZE">"Please directly face the camera throughout the measurement"</string>
    <string name="ERR_CONSTRAINT_MOVEMENT">"Please hold still throughout the measurement"</string>
    <string name="ERR_CONSTRAINT_NO_NETWORK">"To use Anura, please make sure you're connected to WiFi or a mobile network"</string>
    <string name="ERR_CONSTRAINT_POSITION">"Please keep your face centred within the outline throughout the measurement"</string>
    <string name="ERR_CONSTRAINT_TOO_FAR">"Please move closer to the camera and keep your face centred within the outline throughout the measurement"</string>
    <string name="ERR_EMAIL_LOGIN_FAILED">"Email/Password combination is incorrect
Please try again"</string>
    <string name="ERR_EMAIL_NOT_FOUND">"A user with this email address was not found"</string>
    <string name="ERR_MSG_ANALYZER_FAILED">"There was an error analyzing your results
Please try again"</string>
    <string name="ERR_MSG_MEASUREMENT_FAILED">"Anura is unable to process this measurement.
Please check your network connection and try again."</string>
    <string name="ERR_MSG_MEASUREMENT_TIMEOUT">"Data could not be sent for analysis
Please check your network connection and try again."</string>
    <string name="ERR_MSG_NO_NETWORK">"You are not connected to the internet"</string>
    <string name="ERR_MSG_SNR">"The blood flow measurement was not reliable
Please try to allow the light to fall evenly across your face while holding still"</string>
    <string name="ERR_MSG_SNR_SHORT">"Please try to allow the light to fall evenly across your face while holding still"</string>
    <string name="ERR_NOTE_LOAD">"Failed to load note"</string>
    <string name="ERR_NOTE_SAVE">"There was an error saving the note"</string>
    <string name="ERR_PASSWORD_RESET">"Your password could not be reset"</string>
    <string name="ERR_PASSWORD_SHORT">"Your password must be at least {NUM} characters long"</string>
    <string name="ERR_PHONE_NOT_FOUND">"A user with this mobile number was not found"</string>
    <string name="ERR_SERVER_CONNECTION">"Unable to connect to the server"</string>
    <string name="ERR_TIMEOUT">"Please make sure you are connected to WiFi or a mobile network"</string>
    <string name="ERR_TITLE_ANALYZER_FAILED">"Analyzer Failed"</string>
    <string name="ERR_TITLE_MEASUREMENT_FAILED">"Measurement failed"</string>
    <string name="ERR_TITLE_MEASUREMENT_TIMEOUT">"Request timed out"</string>
    <string name="ERR_TURN_OFF_LOW_POWER_MODE">"Please disable Low Power Mode before continuing"</string>

    <string name="WARNING_CONSTRAINT_BACKLIGHT">"The backlight is too strong
Please try changing position so more light falls directly on the face"</string>
    <string name="WARNING_CONSTRAINT_BRIGHTNESS">"Your face is too bright
Please try to dim the lights"</string>
    <string name="WARNING_CONSTRAINT_DARKNESS">"Your face is not well lit
Please try better lighting"</string>
    <string name="WARNING_CONSTRAINT_DISTANCE">"The face is too far
Please try to move closer to the camera"</string>
    <string name="WARNING_CONSTRAINT_EXPOSURE">"Please hold still while the camera is calibrating…"</string>
    <string name="WARNING_CONSTRAINT_FPS">"The camera is not maintaining the required frame rate
Please try closing all background applications"</string>
    <string name="WARNING_CONSTRAINT_GAZE">"Please look directly into the camera"</string>
    <string name="WARNING_CONSTRAINT_MOVEMENT">"Too much movement
Please hold still"</string>
    <string name="WARNING_CONSTRAINT_POSITION">"Try to keep your face within the outline"</string>
    <string name="WARNING_CONSTRAINT_TOO_CLOSE">"Please move a little further away"</string>
    <string name="WARNING_CONSTRAINT_TOO_FAR">"Please move a little closer"</string>
    <string name="WARNING_LOW_POWER_MODE">"For better accuracy, please disable Low Power Mode"</string>
    <string name="WARNING_SERVER_CONNECTION">"Connecting to the server"</string>
    <string name="dfx_id_version">"DFX Extraction Library Version: %1$s\nAnura Core Version: %2$s"</string>

    <string name="your_data_control">Your Data, Your Control</string>
    <string name="data_control_desc">Your health data is safe with us and will only be utilized to customize the content and services we provide.\n\nYour health data will never be shared with any company but RightLife and its partners, and you can delete or manage the data you share with us from your profile any time.\n\nWe may use device identifiers for analytics and to personalise your experience in-app.

We’ll never share your data with anyone outside RightLife and our trusted partners. You can manage or delete your data anytime from your profile.

We also use device identifiers to improve analytics and tailor your in-app experience.</string>

    <string name="data_control_desc1">Your health data stays with us safe, secure, and used only to personalize your experience on RightLife.\n\nWe’ll never share your data with anyone outside RightLife and our trusted partners. You can manage or delete your data anytime from your profile.\n\nWe also use device identifiers to improve analytics and tailor your in-app experience.\n\n</string>

    <string name="str_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="continue_google">Continue With Google</string>

    <!--<string name="know_each_other">Let’s get to know each other</string>-->
    <string name="know_each_other">Let’s get to know you.</string>
    <!--<string name="know_your_name">We’d love to know \nyour name!</string>-->
    <string name="know_your_name">What should we call you?</string>
    <!--<string name="error_username">Invalid user name, do not use number, special characters</string>-->
    <string name="error_username">Invalid name. Please use letters only (no numbers or symbols).</string>
    <string name="happy_to_share">Happy to have you here,</string>
    <string name="wellness_focus">What’s your wellness focus?</string>
    <string name="pick_up_goal">Pick one goal. We’ll take care of the rest.</string>
    <string name="str_think_right">ThinkRight</string>
    <string name="str_move_right">MoveRight</string>
    <string name="str_eat_right">EatRight</string>
    <string name="str_sleep_right">SleepRight</string>
    <string name="boost_mental_clarity">Boost Mental Clarity.</string>
    <string name="stay_active">Stay Active.</string>
    <string name="eat_healthy">Eat Healthier.</string>
    <string name="sleep_better">Sleep Better.</string>
    <string name="your_journey_your_way">Your journey, your way!</string>
    <string name="choose_goals">Pick the one goal that\'s your top priority at the moment.</string>
    <string name="unlock_power">Unlock The Power Of Your Mind</string>

    <string name="other_topics">What other topics interest you?</string>
    <string name="select_your_interest">Select all that apply. You can edit from your profile.</string>
    <string name="save_interest">Save Interests</string>

    <string name="third_filler_screen1_thinkright">"\"Insufficient and excessive sleep were associated with higher depressive symptoms and lower well-being\""</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen2_thinkright">"\"High consumption of refined carbohydrates may increase the risk of depression symptoms.\""</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen3_thinkright">"\"Exercise to enhance memory performs and reduce depression and anxiety.\""</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen4_thinkright">A Calm Mind Is\nJust the Start</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen5_thinkright">Thinking right isn\'t just about quieting your thoughts; it\'s about fueling your body, moving with purpose, and resting deeply.\n\nAt RightLife, we bring this together to make mindfulness a lifestyle, not a moment.</string>

    <string name="third_filler_screen1_sleepright">"\"Individuals with consistent, high-quality sleep reported lower perceived stress\""</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen2_sleepright">"\"Sleep deprivation led to increased calorie consumptions\""</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen3_sleepright">"\"Physical activity aids in stress reduction and promotes better sleep\""</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen4_sleepright">Sleep, But Make It Holistic</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen5_sleepright">Sleep isn’t just what happens at night—it’s influenced by how you move, what you eat, and how you manage your mind. At RightLife, we connect these dots to help you truly rest and recharge.</string>

    <string name="third_filler_screen1_moveright">"\"A meta-analysis in JAMA Psychiatry (2018) revealed that regular physical activity reduced depression risk by 26%\""</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen2_moveright">"\"Individuals engaging in regular aerobic exercise reported significantly lower stress levels\""</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen3_moveright">"\"Regular exercise improved the regulation of hunger and reduced overeating tendencies\""</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen4_moveright">Your Body In Motion, Your Life In Balance</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen5_moveright">Movement fuels energy, builds strength, and even improves your sleep and focus. At RightLife, we weave exercise into your overall wellness, making every move count.</string>

    <string name="third_filler_screen1_eatright">"\"Nutrient-dense foods improves cognitive function and emotional stability.\""</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen2_eatright">"\"Consuming high-fat or high-sugar meals near bedtime delays sleep onset and reduces REM sleep\""</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen3_eatright">"\"A 2023 review in the Journal of Sports Medicine highlighted that carbohydrate intake before exercise improves energy levels\""</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen4_eatright">It’s Not Just About The Plate</string>
    <string name="third_filler_screen5_eatright">Eating right feeds more than hunger—it fuels your mind, powers your movement, and supports restorative sleep. At RightLife, we blend nutrition with every aspect of wellness to make sure your meals work for you.</string>


    <string name="verified_member_text">To become a verified member,\n <b>Complete Your Profile.</b></string>

    <!-- for AI code  -->

    <string name="message_no_network_connected_str">No network connected!</string>
    <string name="message_something_went_wrong_str">Something went wrong!</string>

    <string-array name="am_pm_array">
        <item>AM</item>
        <item>PM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="underlined_change"><u>Change</u></string>
    <string name="title_activity_content_details">ContentDetailsActivity</string>

    <string name="sleep_intro">
        Understanding your sleep is essential to optimizing recovery and overall well-being.
        Your Sleep Analysis in <b>RightLife</b> provides a detailed breakdown of your sleep performance, consistency, and recovery.
    </string>

    <string name="sleep_performance">
        Your sleep performance measures how much sleep you got versus how much you needed based on your body’s demands.\n
        • <b>Sleep Needed</b> – Adjusts dynamically based on recent activity levels, strain, and recovery needs.\n
        • <b>Sleep Obtained</b> – The total time you slept during the night.\n
        RightLife calculates your sleep performance score as a percentage of your actual sleep relative to your goal.
        <b>Aim for 85% or higher</b> to optimize recovery and energy levels.
    </string>

    <string name="sleep_consistency">
        Sleep consistency measures how regularly you go to bed and wake up within a set window.\n
        • <b>Higher consistency</b> helps regulate your circadian rhythm.\n
        • <b>Lower consistency</b> contributes to fatigue, poor recovery, and cognitive decline.\n
        RightLife tracks a <b>4-day rolling sleep consistency</b> to provide insights.
    </string>

    <string name="sleep_stages">
        Your sleep is divided into four stages:\n
        • <b>Awake</b> – Time awake during the night.\n
        • <b>Light Sleep</b> – Supports memory consolidation.\n
        • <b>Deep Sleep</b> – Vital for recovery and immunity.\n
        • <b>REM Sleep</b> – Important for cognition and emotion.
    </string>

    <string name="restorative_sleep">
        <b>Restorative sleep</b> includes Deep Sleep + REM Sleep.\n
        • <b>Deep Sleep</b> supports muscle repair and hormone regulation.\n
        • <b>REM Sleep</b> improves memory and emotional processing.\n
        A high percentage of restorative sleep means <b>efficient recovery</b>.
    </string>

    <string name="rightlife_does">
        🔹 <b>Calculates Sleep Need</b> – Adjusted dynamically.\n
        🔹 <b>Evaluates Sleep Performance</b> – Measures your actual sleep vs. need.\n
        🔹 <b>Analyzes Consistency</b> – Tracks sleep/wake regularity.\n
        🔹 <b>Tracks Sleep Stages</b> – Light, Deep, REM (Wearable only).\n
        🔹 <b>Monitors Restorative Sleep</b> – Deep + REM Sleep impact.
    </string>

    <string name="what_to_do">
        ✅ <b>Maintain a Regular Sleep Schedule</b> – Bedtime/wake within 30–60 minutes.\n
        ✅ <b>Track Sleep</b> – Enable wearable or log manually.\n
        ✅ <b>Aim for 85%+ Sleep Performance</b> – Hit your sleep target.\n
        ✅ <b>Improve Restorative Sleep</b> – Create a good sleep environment.\n
        ✅ <b>Monitor Trends</b> – Use consistency scores and trend arrows.\n\n
        Better sleep = <b>better recovery, sharper focus, improved performance</b>.
    </string>


</resources>